<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Voices Unveiled</title>
    <link>https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Voices Unveiled</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Echoes of Defiance</title>
      <link>https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/echoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/echoes/</guid>
      <description>In the cavernous expanse of the corporate jungle, I tread lightly, an unwelcome intruder. Each step I take feels like tiptoeing through a minefield of expectations, where the slightest misstep could detonate the fragile facade of acceptance I&amp;rsquo;ve constructed.&#xA;My voice, a symphony of unheard melodies, echoes through the sterile corridors, drowned out by the thunderous applause for those who fit the mold. They speak in tongues of authority, their language foreign to my ears, leaving me stranded on the outskirts of comprehension.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I am who I am</title>
      <link>https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/whoiam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/whoiam/</guid>
      <description>I always felt a bit different from everyone else, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out what exactly it was. Most of my friends were girls, and my guy friends were limited. I was more emotional than the rest, which could be seen as an easy way to exploit me.&#xA;Growing up, you are often mocked for any sort of difference that you have. Hair colour, different clothes, different shoes, different food. When growing up in the early 2000s-2010s, there was a new &amp;ldquo;cool and hip way&amp;rdquo; to mock people, and that was through their language.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyranny of Language</title>
      <link>https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/tyranny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/tyranny/</guid>
      <description>In the lexicon of life, a grim tableau,&#xA;Where words can wound, and spirits low.&#xA;In every phrase, a dagger&amp;rsquo;s thrust,&#xA;Power&amp;rsquo;s hand, in language&amp;rsquo;s rust.&#xA;In boardroom meetings, where suits convene,&#xA;Language dictates who reigns supreme.&#xA;The one who speaks with confidence, bold,&#xA;Controls the narrative, as stories unfold.&#xA;On streets where whispers fade to naught,&#xA;The silenced masses, battles fought.&#xA;Their voices stifled, dreams suppressed,&#xA;By language&amp;rsquo;s tyranny, they&amp;rsquo;re oppressed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Simple Word</title>
      <link>https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/oneword/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:20:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/oneword/</guid>
      <description>For women, there seems to be a point in their lives where they are confronted with how their body will represent them. I remember being 8 years old the first time I really felt this. I spent the day at the park, one that had a splash pad. The type that was a really shallow, wading pool with a bunch of sprinklers and an area to run around. I was a total fish as a kid, I loved swimming and being in the water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo</title>
      <link>https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/tattoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/tattoo/</guid>
      <description>Four words. Anytime I look down to my arm, I am reminded of four words&#xA;I love myself today.&#xA;They stare back at me in deep black. The letters grow closer together with every passing day. They are a little crooked. They are not perfect. The s is a little thicker than the y. There is a freckle above the l.&#xA;These words pierced me. Scratching my veins. It hurt and it made me bleed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The lesser man</title>
      <link>https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/lesser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lucasmei.github.io/voices_unveiled/posts/lesser/</guid>
      <description>The lesser man is trapped in the expectations of society, forced to exist only within the confines of what others place. A tall picket fence with no escape. The people didn&amp;rsquo;t make the fence. He made the fence to protect himself from people.&#xA;The lesser man grows tired of being tired, but has grown tired of others. He can no longer go to others because of this fatigue, so he continues writing to himself about himself.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
